

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

CHRISTIAN A.SANCHEZ

GET IN CONTACT

Home: 04-517-1978 Mobile: 096-3787611 Mail: christianabrahamsanchez@gmail.com GitHub: Chrisnewgear (github.com) Web: https://christiansanchezcv.netlify.app

Current address: Cdla. Colinas de la Alborada Mz. 726 V. 18

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a autodidact Junior Frontend Developer with 1 year of experience, with skills in interactive design with 3 years of experience. I am also passionate and willing to learn new technologies to enhance my skills in coding and design, furthermore I'm studying software developing career at "Tecnológico Universitario ARGOS".

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- HTML, CSS, MySQL, SQL Server, JavaScript, jQuery, Git, GitHub, Debian based Linux Distros. Materialize, OOP, Blazor Framework, C#.
- Basic knowledge of PHP, JAVA, C, C++, React, Design Systems, MVC, Entity Framework.
- Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro, Adobe XD, Figma
- · PCs, laptops & Mac repairing.

OTHER SKILLS

- The ability to analyze complex technical information
- Detail oriented
- · Excellent problem solver
- Drawing & Illustration
- Soft skills
- English C1 level

WORK EXPERIENCE LISTOSOFT

Jr. Fullstack Web Developer (Currently)

· ERP Web Version Development

ALTURA

SQL Administrator | June 2022 - January 2023

- SQL DBs management
- Frontend developer

TEDU (AGRICULTORES DEL ECUADOR)

Frontend Developer | 2021 - 2022

- · Frontend developer
- · Technical support & consulting

UTEG

Clerk | 2019-2020

- Customer service
- · Technical support

BANCO GUAYAQUIL

Senior Assistant | 2005 - 2016

- Document digitalization department
- Clearing house
- Legal requirements
- Technical support

EDUCATION HISTORY

ESCUELA POLITÉCNICA DEL LITORAL

System Analyst, 2005-2006 (Dropped out)

TECNOLÓGICO UNIVERSITARIO ARGOS

Software Development (Currently)

SELF-TOUGHT LEARNING

UDEMY

Web Development with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, AJAX, PHP, SQL.

PI AT7

- Software Development School (Currently)
- Web Development School (Currently)

OPEN BOOTCAMP

• Frontend Development (Currently)